[music]
How's it going, Ray? Nice to meet you.
Very well.
Thanks for thanks for taking the time to
uh to to chat with us about this stuff.
I'm really excited to to hear what side
of these, you know, different paths
you're going to lead us down and then uh
maybe we'll make some decisions on where
we think which path that we're going to
go down.
Absolutely. I mean, that's what I want
to do is just get us having uh better
conversations more than today. While I
do have a point of view, um it's really
more about how do we how do we approach
the the chaotic
um diversity of points of view in this
space and as you mentioned I'm currently
chief architect at All Hands AI. We have
a coding agent called Open Hands, which
actually this week was just shot back to
the top of the Sweetbench verified
leaderboard and is the only open source
agent in the top 10. But I'm here today
to talk about something different. And
as I was putting this together, I
realized this is not even an AI talk.
And this is perhaps not really a
programming talk either. This is a talk
about empathy and this is a talk about
listening to each other. But if that
sounds uncomfortable then don't worry
because we will have AI and programming
in the uh you know as a backdrop a nice
comfy backdrop for these concepts and
let's start a little bit where with
where I felt I was coming from this is a
day in the life of an AI skeptic.
someone will say something uh very
provocative publicly like um recently
you might have seen the anthropic CEO's
remarks on you know many different
topics many different professions one
quote that we saw a lot was in 12 months
we may be in a world where AI is writing
essentially all the code I think we've
got 10 months remaining on the clock
there um so when we hear things like
this we have questions I I would
definitely encourage you to check out
Cal Forser's talk on this track as well
about you know the other 70% of
engineering because those of us who have
you know been in the field are aware
that just writing essentially all the
code isn't the entirety of the job
there's a lot of different room for
interpretation here but regardless we
hear things like this we have questions
I um posed a particular uh kind of
playful challenge about okay if we can
do all the code can we kill one main
frame can we uh replace the code in just
a single mainframe. Half of the US GDP
is still tied up in companies that use
mainframes in some capacity.
Really the specifics of my challenge not
really important. Um just for the last
two years, what I have been repeatedly
saying is that language models break old
code. I've been saying that in every way
I know how and testing that assumption
and and trying to find ways around it. I
see this as the central uh problem we
have to tackle bringing AI into software
development is that code needs to
continue to develop. Develop as a
synonym for change. We can't just be
thinking about can we make some new
prototype? What are we going to do with
something that uh already exists? And
when I bring up what I see are pretty
basic um facts and questions in that
regard. Um, all sorts of things are
hurled at me. I I am called a lite. I'm
told I have my head in the sand. I'm
told I'm missing the big picture. And at
this point, like I literally work on
coding agents full-time. So, if I'm a
lite, I don't know what you want from
us, you know, but uh in particular in
response to the last post, you know,
mostly positive feedback, but one person
the full quote was missing the big
picture. so badly that it physically
hurts them to read my post. It doesn't
feel great to be talked to in this way.
You perhaps have um also seen this one
maybe many hundreds of times, the
phrase, you'll be left behind if you
don't, you know, subscribe to their
newsletter or or use their um preferred
type of tool or whatever it might be.
You're going to be left behind. I mean,
this is language that is better suited
for an apocalyptic religious prophecy in
the form of a bem movie series featuring
Kirk Cameron than some kind of nuanced
technical discussion. Um, I don't like
telling people they're going to be left
behind. I also saw this this phrase said
with more or less a straight face,
resistance is futile. said by someone
with like some really respectable
accomplishments. Someone whose work that
I admire and might even be one of the
speakers at this event. I'm not sure. Um
I don't know what to do with this when I
see things like this. I mean, for all
the money in the bank, you might recall
who said resistance is futile. Who is
being quoted here? Was it said by the
heroes of that story? I mean, no. It was
said by the Borg,
one of the most notorious villains in
the history of science fiction.
If we find ourselves quoting them in
earnest, you know, are we really on the
right side?
Jeanluke Peard would never say
resistance is futile. He only said that
as lucudis when the AI was controlling
his brain. Um, and in the story,
resistance wasn't futile at all. They
did resist and they were successful.
Jean Luke Pequard would say, "If you are
on the side of truth, resist to the last
breath." But okay, we need to breathe.
[laughter] I need to slow down. I'm just
responding to emotionally charged
rhetoric with other emotionally charged
rhetoric. And before I know it, it's 9
in the morning and I'm already worked up
on LinkedIn. Um,
I chose to become involved in this
dialogue. I believed that I had some
insight as a legacy code expert and if
I'm going to make any headway in that
dialogue, I I need to be able to engage
with people who think about things
somewhat differently than I do. They
also believe they're in the right. They
also mean well. they have a different
view based on their own reflection of
the answers to certain questions and
they're maybe trying to warn against
some things as well. So what are we even
talking about? It all hinges on, you
know, just sort of different answers
we've come up with to this fundamental
question that's all brought us here
together to have the these awesome
discussions which is the future of
software in light of
the AI changes recently, in light of a
lot of other pieces on the board. Um so
in service of that dialogue I have found
that is really helpful to just lay out
what the viewpoints are that we see
people clustering around and then we can
identify okay well you're in that camp
over here that's why you're saying
things that are so different to what I
think here and and we can start to uh we
can start untangle things. So, I'm going
to name these scenarios first and then
we'll get into all of them and perhaps
you'll have different names for some of
these, but I'm calling them these. One
is extreme completion. Two is the
deocalypse.
Three is abstraction leap. Four is
uncharted waters. Five is the review
economy. Six is the infinite pile of
garbage.
So perhaps the most conservative
uncontroversial
outcome here is the extreme completion
because it is already happened uh to a
fairly significant degree. This is
things like your coding assistants that
you appear in IDE and editors and um
more recently you've had the coding
agents which have a little more autonomy
but basically is is bound to completing
your your immediate thought on a
tactical level and they're operated by
programmers. The AI does the typing but
ultimately if this is all that happens
our job doesn't fundamentally change.
you still need a great deal of of coding
expertise to use these in a sustainable
way on an existing codebase. Um, a great
convenience, but
ultimately not a gamecher to the degree
that many people think we can achieve.
This is an example of it. This is the
cursor editor. It's quite popular. And
here I am doing some autocomplete action
on some Haskell code where I've got one
function that already exists and I would
like to make another one clean prime
prime that will remove both leading and
trailing spaces. Sure enough, with the
help of cloud sonnet, it um plops that
out. It it is perfectly serviceable
code, but I'm you know making a
suggestion at a pretty small micro level
in order to do that. Um the reason by
the way that I'm using um an example in
the programming language Haskell is
because it has very advanced type
checking and I think type theory is a
very rich area to provide uh checks that
form kind of a counterbalance against
the non-deterministic nature of language
model output. So that's food for
thought. But
um then we have more agentic examples
and there are a number of these. The one
I happen to work on is open hands and uh
this is something I did just yesterday
where we do this with just routine tasks
and this is just a new way of
interacting with it. It's a slack um
chat integration that's experimental and
I um I said hey we recently had to
update this log statement in this
particular way. Um, there are probably
others in the codebase that need to be
updated in that same way. Um, ca can you
go make a PR that does that? Comes back
a few minutes later with a whole 48 file
pull request for me to look at. Um,
that's even going to the extent of like
it wrote scripts on its own to help it
find the cases it needed to change. Very
interesting stuff. I mean, this this is
nuts. if you'd have showed this to me a
couple years ago. And albeit it's a
small kind of tactical request, but even
to be able to have this kind of
allpurpose tech that dirt shoveler
really cool. And there are multiple
agents that can take on in a codebase of
this size about 100,000 lines um tasks
um even more sophisticated than than
this. This is um fairly low ball for for
what it could do. Um again
[clears throat] that's all though in the
extreme completion camp. I argue that
would not fundamentally change uh the
world of software development. It would
be a great convenience and and is worth
doing. Um a more extreme point of view
is the devocalypse.
Now when some of us get in these
contentious arguments I think it is
often on one side or the other are
believers in the dev apocalypse the
developer apocalypse. Um
so that is there is no longer anything
really even resembling the role of a
software engineer as we see it today or
it's highly specialized very few of
them. Um however it's not an apocalypse
to everyone. This is also important to
understand to many people in the
pipeline it is the innovator's paradise
right our elimination is their
empowerment perhaps in their eyes right
like if they are a product manager if
they are an entrepreneur and they can go
directly from having an idea and
designing it to using it and selling it
to people that seems very great right we
of course feel like hey why wouldn't
anyone Doesn't everyone want to work
with us? Well, I mean, I don't know.
Sometimes we're very expensive and
cranky. [laughter]
So, um, this contention of like who
wants what in the conversation also is
is an impass to us understanding each
other because
um, we can say, look, it's not going to
be able to replace all of the work
because you just don't understand all
the things we do. there are scale and
sustainability concerns and so on and
they will think you're just saying that
because you want to keep your job. Well,
okay, I do want my friends to keep their
job, but I don't think that's the only
reason we're saying what we're saying. I
I think there is legitimately subtlety
to managing complex piles of software
and a lot of unanswered questions in how
machines could let um people without
certain skills take over that.
But to argue for the de apocalypse we
have to know how it would actually be
brought about. So this brings us to the
next scenario which is abstraction leap.
This is essentially um the notion that
in the same sense that we used to write
assembly language and now we write in
higher level languages that there will
be another leap of a similar magnitude
such that what we now think of as source
code will be somewhat of an inconvenient
detail to most of the people. Most of
the time it would be almost as
specialized as as diving into LLVM bite
code or or assembly or something like
that.
Um that's that's very interesting. How
would that occur? Many people believe
that that we're already seeing it. It's
prompts. Prompts are the new um source
code. LLMs are the new compilers some
say. And um [clears throat] that's how
standard source code is now like
assembly language. um natural language
becomes the artifact we maintain somehow
it is structured somehow and and tested
and the objection to this is usually and
I I fall into this camp that this is
just not predictable enough to scale
that it works on and and small or low
stakes situations but uh it's not really
something you can build on language
models do not constitute an abstraction
because an abstraction needs to be
robust robust enough that you can not be
constantly pulled back into
implementation details.
People do have other points of view.
They believe that we'll be able to solve
that problem. It's unclear to me how,
but you know, it's not impossible. Um,
here is an example that seemed pretty
promising from back in 2022. This is a a
some source code from paper called
Parcel. If you go there and look up this
source code, you can see 61 lines of of
structured prompts that have turned into
an entire lisp interpreter and about 200
lines of Python.
And as you can see in these these
functions are not being defined with any
source code, just the um description of
what they do and an example of input and
output.
And then you you see parse has a utility
function that's being you know kind of
indented under it. And there's many
levels of these indentations.
That's very interesting to me actually.
It does seem like it's a legitimate
attempt to make this prompts code thing
more robust, more scalable.
Will be we be able to actually
productize this? There are a number of
of you know a number of attempts. We'll
see where that goes.
I think a more plausible way we could
achieve abstraction leap is with DSLs or
domain specific languages.
Now, if you're not familiar with DSLs,
you probably already are familiar with
them. If you've used developerf facing
ones such as SQL, such as regular
expressions and um most office workers
to some degree use uh the world's most
popular DSL which is uh Microsoft Excel,
right? The spreadsheet is is also a form
of DSL um and there are many more
specialized ones to particular business
domains. So what this is is an upfront
investment in making a very specialized
programming environment that makes
expressing certain kinds of thoughts
very efficient and this empowers domain
experts.
This has kind of interesting cost
trade-offs that has improved over the
last 20 years with the advent of things
like language workbenches they're called
which are specialized tools for making
programming environments of this kind
and uh there's also like some call it a
paradigm called languageoriented
programming. These are some uh tools
that are in that space. It's um easy to
imagine that language models, and
there's been some work on this already,
will both speed up the process of making
these DSLs and also provide this um
automated completion for the people who
are using it.
This is um a video on the right by me
from my YouTube channel Craft Versus
Croft talking about why I I kind of
dedicated 2025 to studying DSLs on that
channel. And this from uh on the left is
a talk called empowerment of subject
matter experts by Marcus Volter. And uh
he is one of the the big experts in in
that space done uh done a lot of
different custom DSL implementations. So
these are areas that are pretty
interesting to look at now I think
but what doesn't um that's an example
with abstraction leap it's still code
under the hood ultimately we're still in
charted waters there the next scenario
is uncharted waters many people believe
that AI will create a future of coding
that is not even codelike actually it's
a f future of computing perhaps even
without code what does that even mean I
I'm still kind of struggling with it.
Some people believe that model inference
just the uh the neural network as the
execution engine instead of the CPU will
become a more prevalent um model of
computation. Uh then
you have the idea maybe AI will get so
sophisticated that's it's inventing new
programming paradigms and we can't even
conceive of it. I I hear a lot of these
ideas and I guess it's just hard for me
to run away with it without having more
concrete uh notion of what it will look
like and to be able to prove it at
scale. So,
um I think it's prevalent enough we must
acknowledge this this point of view that
the future is going to be something
that's just not at all like the past. I
just I really I have trouble being asked
to prepare for it if uh we can't
establish it more concretely than that.
So moving back down to earth is a
concept I call a review economy
which is already happening to some
degree as we are able to create more and
more coding suggestions.
We are now limited by our ability to
validate them. Right? We have agents, we
have co-pilot assistants
pushing these um suggested changes of
kind of questionable validity but um
lots of speed at us and we are you know
in the in the extreme version our job is
just reduced to checking and reviewing
and reviewing and reviewing this machine
output.
Um, that's kind of a dismal future to
many people. Like I I don't think we
necessarily want this. I also
don't see it as an endgame so much as a
pit stop. I think if we wind up with
anything that looks like this, we have
just failed to manage our bottlenecks.
Well, we need to be going further to the
left here and figure out, okay, how can
we get the uh system to be giving us
suggestions that are right more of the
time such that we're not constrained in
this way or maybe we need to prioritize
them to be looking at the most valuable
first. Um, a pro tip here is if you're
not familiar with the the body of
knowledge theory of constraints, anytime
your your your life looks like this with
a big choke point, you know, uh the
thinking processes introduced in theory
of constraints are are very helpful for
analyzing the situation.
So finally we have the most dismal
scenario, the infinite pile of garbage,
which is where AI has made it very
efficient to create code of dubious
quality to the point where our products
get worse and worse over time instead of
better. And we are ultimately just sort
of crushed by this mountain of tech debt
that not even the AI can help us build
or um dig our way back out of.
there's some support uh for the notion
that we might be heading there. For
example, this is a white paper by
uplevel where they have done some
controlled experiment where they've
given some subsection of um developers
access to co-pilot and seen they had a
much higher bug rate and their progress
through issues was relatively
consistent. I mean that would be a
terrible outcome, right? is if even the
perceived productivity gain weren't
there, but quality plummeted. Um
hopefully that's not the case, right?
But that was what they saw. Um, Git
Clear also has a white paper and they um
did more of a metrics approach here and
and in in analyzing code historically
they found that 2024 in their records
was the first year that there was more
uh copy and pasted equivalent code than
there was moved code. That's kind of
scary if you've seen what the results of
that can be. Again, there can be
rebuttals that like AI coding assistance
simply changed the dynamic of what we
should expect. Maybe the duplication's
no longer so unmaintainable. I think
that would need to be established for us
to say it confidently. Right now, I
think we just need to get to the bottom
of um of this and and figure out, you
know, does it need to continue to
happen? But these are just a couple of
white papers from a couple of maybe
self-interested parties.
Not everyone thinks that.
Unsurprisingly, GitHub does not believe
that GitHub co-pilot decreases quality.
They think it increases it. And they
have this blog where they've also done
an experiment um not this time on um
work on production code
things. Their rating of the quality
improved by by using co-pilot. Um,
obviously they and maybe the others too
are are self-interested observers. Maybe
even so am I. Um, we need to figure out
what's going on is is my takeaway here.
I I want to be able to come back and be
citing actual papers and not just white
papers and hopefully like a metaanalysis
of good research papers. If you know of
some work in the space, I would love to
get in touch with you.
Um,
and in the meantime, I think we're
better off studying just past work on
developer productivity than to think
that we get to and code quality. Then we
to think we need to rewrite all of the
rules with AI and start from no
knowledge at all. People will um look at
these and say, "Okay, it's maybe
producing dubious quality or more bugs
now, but it will get better." I I say we
will need to make it better in order for
it to be better. The models will have
more capabilities but we need to use
them very judiciously. We need to engage
in careful design.
Um, so
getting to the end here once again the
scenarios that I've identified you might
see others or want to call them
different things are extreme completion
debocalypse also known as innovators
paradise abstraction leap uncharted
waters the review economy and infinite
pile of garbage we won't just go to one
of these places we'll probably go to
several in in different ways they
interact right so for instance Many
people believe that extreme completion
will um become the sort of vibe coding
revolution where it leads to the
depocalypse and others are worried that
we will miss that outcome and it will
drive us into infinite pile of garbage.
I um have expressed like if any of these
are going to completely transform
programming, it might be carefully
designed abstractions in the abstraction
leaf scenario combined with our
completion capabilities.
Um but again there will be multiple
things that happen and they will affect
different sectors of the industry
differently. So someone might have a
very different point of view than you
and still be right within the area that
they're thinking of.
And we get a say in what the outcome's
going to be. I don't want us to
sit here and feel as though we are just
waiting for a meteor to hit us.
developers are kind of uniquely
positioned to be
engineering our own future rather than
waiting for it. So I think we need to
get a clear vision of of what our goals
are. What do we want from software in
the world? Do we want more developers?
Do we want fewer? Do we want software to
be of high quality or do we just need
more of it no matter what quality is?
What what are we really demanding from
the system? I want many things from
software. I want it to work well. I want
it to be valuable to its users and to
the people who are building it. And I
want people who work together to treat
each other well.
Um well, thank you very much. I look
forward to your questions.
Okay. Well, hey, how's it going? Thank
you so much, Ray. I've got to say that
was incredibly enjoyable. It was just
really fun just uh
hearing you go through uh you know, all
of those things. And uh it's definitely
got me thinking about what I want. Like
I personally love the democratization of
software. And so that's one of the
reasons that I'm excited about a pathway
we can work out to take AI to actually
help with that. Like a lot of my career
has been in the world of of the web like
I worked on Chrome and the like and it
was exciting to try and get as many
people as possible um actually doing
development. But um yeah really
interesting to to think through these
things. So, okay, we got let's get to we
don't have a lot of time, so let's jump
in with a question here from David. Uh,
what do you think is the single most
impactful thing we can do to reach the
best eventual outcome and avoid the
worst?
Yeah. Well, I'll tell you what I spent a
lot of last year doing is I uh briefly
abandoned AI and studied formal methods
for the year. I like I went and learned
theorem provers. Um and then I and then
I went and worked for an AI coding agent
company only after going on that side
quest. Right. So um basically if I was
to generalize that into advice, I mean
do learn theorem provers if you have the
stomach for it. Really uh intriguing
stuff. But just like let's not pretend
the rest of computer science doesn't
exist and the rest of human
understanding does not exist. Let's like
not use this as an excuse to
not um study what we already know. A lot
of the problems, a lot of the gaps that
LLMs leave are filled by other areas of
understanding if we just let that
happen. Um and we don't look for all of
the answers within, you know, whatever
the newest brand of AI is.
Yeah, that makes sense. Awesome. Oops.
Um, so, uh, one question I had is you
you mentioned at the beginning and
you've sprinkled in a couple of times
that you work, uh, for Open Hands, uh,
but folks may not actually know what
that is and the history. I think it was
Open Devon back in the day. Like, I'd
love to for you to just share a little
bit about um, what Open Hands is and
what you're up to there.
Yeah. And you know, we're we're in a um
this area where back in the day is a
year ago, [laughter]
you know, like that's what we refer to
as back in the day is amazing. Um like
earlier I said back in 2022, like it was
the you know, dark ages. Um, so yes,
Cognition Labs announced Devon, uh, a
proprietary tool, um, in I think it was
March or April of last year, and they
announced it as the world's first AI
software engineer, a term many of us
deeply disagree with. [laughter]
Um and
then however we were very intrigued by
the kind of value proposition they have
of this thing that autonomously carries
out your tasks. We had been using these
uh things where we're like kind of
copying and pasting broken stuff into
chat and we recognized like if we can
just have the LM like fight through
these errors it'll be much better. We
know we can do better. So the product
direction was super influential and um
it kind of became this rallying cry of
let's create an open-source one of those
and several groups including um the
people that made SWEBench at Princeton
and uh then this this group came
together with open hands um yeah that
was originally open Devon the like can
can the open source community produce
one of these that's competitive that is
achieving the same scores and it did um
in very short order and that ultimately
became a company and I I went from
cheering them on to to joining them.
Nice. So a lot of the AI companies talk
about you know how much of the code of
their product is written by their
product and the like like how can you
share anything of how you use open uh
hands with to build open hands and how
that's gone and the the pros and cons
and all those things.
Yeah. Yeah. that I mean that could be
its own um interview just on that topic.
But briefly like some of our recent blog
um posts if you go to um all-ashands.dev
uh actually do discuss that opens is by
the numbers the biggest contributor to
its own codebase currently. Albeit there
is always you know a developer who's
prompting it. But some of them are are
kind of fire and forget pull requests.
Like we just tag it in an issue. It
comes back with something. We might tag
it a few more times with things we want
to change. But that's like kind of the
best case scenario is when the task is
carved out enough that we can do that. I
also use it for investigations a lot
though like um can you you know poke
around? I'm getting this error. Can you
poke around and give me some ideas about
why that might be happening? Um so there
are more interactive flows as as well
but it's um for things that are like in
editor work we're still using uh you
know tools like like cursor because we
have kind of intentionally chosen to
operate in the outer loop the more
autonomous workflows uh we are not
trying to be the best uh you know
development environment for for coding
interactively.
Got it. What about the role of of test?
Sometimes I've found myself where folks
have come and been like, "Hey, like um
my developers don't like writing tests."
So if your tool could like write a lot
of tests, that'd be really great. And
then wait, if we have all these tests,
then we can like have a great it's like
well it's bit of a chicken and egg there
too. If the AI is writing both of these
like what what's your experience been
around, you know, the role of tests with
with AI?
So I um I come from a a background like
my first job I did the extreme
programming methodology for seven years
test driven development pair programming
and everything. So like I have a lot of
thoughts on testing right I do I do
value it heavily. Um I love that coding
agents can help me write tests. I don't
love that they don't do it unless I ask
them to. I think that is in this whole
space like I'm just I'm calling us out
not any particular players like
it's not going to have good results that
like our tools by default when they ask
or you ask them for something are
currently most of them giving you know
okay here's some untested code like the
systemic result of that will be that
people are writing less tests. I do love
that when you choose to do the right
thing it will help you. Um, there's also
traps you can fall into of like, am I
not writing the the tests that are going
to give me the best outcome? Am I just
getting code coverage for its own sake?
But that was kind of always here with
this. So, um,
yeah, a good with the with the fix loop.
Um, it could be fascinating when I I
feel like it's easy for developers to
just grab a stack trace, you know, from
a failed test, say, throw it in to AI
and just say, "Fix this."
And it doesn't have the right system
prompt around it for fixing or whatever,
and then it'll come in. There was just
one recently where
um that kind of fix was it was all about
localization and it would do create a
solution just for the Turkish language
for this particular letter and then the
test pass we're back to 100% test
passing right rather than actually
understanding the the core problem and
and fixing the core problem right and
when go in there you can you do do you
see those kind of things as well where
it like lots of feelgood you know lots
of green but not necessarily,
you know, getting the the level of
quality.
Yeah. I mean, we've we see more extreme
things uh than that. I, you know, I've
seen a a variety of these tools. Again,
this is like the coding agents in
general are known to pass tests by
deleting entire areas of functionality.
Like, well, the thing you're asking me
to execute successfully would work if I
just deleted all this stuff, right? And
that's not common, but it's not unheard
of either. Like if you've been around
the block with these, you've probably
seen that happen. Um, that's scary, you
know, but it's again, it's only scary
depending on how you you manage your
process. Like, are you going if you if
you catch that in review, incredibly
easy. It's the subtle bugs that I'm more
worried about, but it does, you know, it
gives you an impression of the kind of
leash we need to have these on right
now.
That makes sense. Okay, we got time for
one more question from the from the
crowd here. Radica saying, "Do you think
relying on GitHub Copilot too much might
make developers too dependent on AI or
does it just free up time to focus on
more complex problems?"
Yes.
[laughter]
Um,
so
you've heard these kinds of arguments
come up with just a variety of
conveniences that have happened over the
years and the criticism is right in some
ways and it misses the point in others.
But I would say that
pedagogy is, you know, the study of how
we learn is more complex than are we
doing something that's hard or not. You
do need to to do things that are
challenging in order to really learn
about what's going on. But
just looking for the things that are the
most mundane pain in in your rear end uh
doesn't by itself mean you're learning
the most. You know, we need to treat
learning as its first class uh as a
first class thing that it is.
Awesome. Well, Ray, thank you so much.
That was really thoughtprovoking and and
interesting and uh really appreciate you
taking the time to to share that with
us.
Thanks for having me.
Yeah. Cheers.